<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Gandhi meeting</string>
    <string name="person1Name">Elsy Dayany Guerrero</string>
    <string name="person2Name">Gilberto David Garcia</string>
    <string name="person3Name">Genesis Paola Hernandez</string>
    <string name="person4Name">Pepe</string>
    <string name="person5Name">Alejandro Estrada Balderas</string>
    <string name="person6Name">Dulce Alin Mendez</string>
    <string name="person7Name">Daniel Hernandez</string>
    <string name="person8Name">Juan David Betancourt</string>
    <string name="person9Name">Angel Daza Morales</string>
    <string name="person10Name">Karla Alejandra Aradillas</string>
    <string name="person11Name">Marco Hernandez</string>
    <string name="person12Name">Azael Hernandez Ruiz</string>

    <string name="person1Description">
        She is a nice and fun girl, has a little anxiety and stress, but nothing she hasn\'t been able to deal with,
        her favorite thing to do is making crafts by hand, you would impress how she could pay attention to something
        and making origami at the same time
    </string>

    <string name="person2Description">
        He is a really fun guy (and also gay), you could be laughing for hours along him, he is really creative when
        saying funny things. You would impress how good he is in Halo, did you know he achieved all the halo\'s in
        legendary?
    </string>

    <string name="person3Description">
        She is a funny girl, very intelligent and dedicated to her school. She doesn\'t have many friends but the ones she has
        are very loyal. If you want to contact her by WhatsApp you\'ll have to wait a few hours because she is really a busy person,
        she has to deal with a lot of TikTok and Facebook media, but by the time she\'ll answer, don\'t worry, she will …
        someday she will … will she?
    </string>

    <string name="person4Description">
        He doesn\'t need introduction, pepe is pepe, you dont even deserve to look at him!
    </string>

    <string name="person5Description">
        He is a nice and innocent boy, the most important thing for him is family, and he\'ll do whatever it takes to help them,
        he is a dedicated student, has many friends around, and it\'s because he can be too social, if you ever get to know him,
        it won\'t take any long him to introduce himself towards you
    </string>

    <string name="person6Description">
        She is a curious and a little weird girl, just like Gandhi! in some ways…, she likes surreal things, always wears black wearing,
        she is a hard worker when talking jobs, I sometimes cannot imagine how she can work 12 hours for 3 days, I wouldn\'t be able to!
        You would be surprised if you knew that she is the most interesting girl Gandhi has ever met
    </string>

    <string name="person7Description">
        He is an interesting man, he knows many things you don\'t!, he likes reading web sites and curious things about every type,
        he has really good liking in music, even Gandhi copied some of it. You wouldn\'t believe me if I told you that he can
        know what kind of car it is just watching it or even, listening to the motor noise!
    </string>

    <string name="person8Description">
        He is a nice guy, is also a hard worker, when finished his high school, he started working in a Chinese restaurant which, for those
        who do not know, is a relly heavy and stress work, Gandhi sometimes go to sleep thinking about how David hasn\'t quit that job yet,
        with not doubt, he is a really strong guy!
    </string>

    <string name="person9Description">
        He is a loyal person and one of the funniest persons in the world, not really intelligent, but it doesn\'t matter because
        he can make friends wherever he goes, and that is one of the most important things for him, have friend he can be with,
        He is a little confused and concerned about what he will do or be in the future, but certainly, by the time, he\'ll sure know
    </string>

    <string name="person10Description">
        She is a charismatic girl, she will always give you a smile whenever you talk to her, she has many interesting things to say, so
        if you ever talk to her, don\'t surprise if time passes fast. She is also a dedicated student, excellent notes, and besides
        she knows what she wants, and that\'s a point above many girls!
    </string>

    <string name="person11Description">
        Certainly, one the most intelligent man Gandhi has known, he not only knows about computers, cars, video games, also about chemistry!
        he is a really great person who any one would like to meet, because he knows how to listen/help people, if you ever need a
        shoulder where to cry, his are the best
    </string>

    <string name="person12Description">
        He is a weird and intelligent boy, he might seem a little unhappy at the first time but once you know him it\'s totally the opposite,
        he talks to a lot of people (men or women). He is also dedicated to programming and drawing, likes to share his every day things, and also
        likes to make questions to every one, if you ever have the lucky to meet him, don\'t hesitate to feel free to say what you think, he will listen
    </string>

</resources>